I am a graphic designer based in New York. I specialize in typography, branding, website design, and photography. With a keen eye for detail and a passion for creating visually compelling experiences, I bring creativity and innovation to every project.

Experience

Office of Luke Bulman, Designer

June 2024-present New York, US

Editorial Design

Volume 6 & 7 of the book series *Bioclimatic Ceramic Assemblies* for the Architectural Ceramic Assemblies Workshop (ACAW).

(June 2024-present)

Media Matters in Landscape Architecture, a book edited by Karen M'Closkey and Keith VanDerSys. (August 2024-present)

Cover Design

Cover design for Form and Fortification: The Art of Military Architecture in Renaissance Italy, Book by Morgan Ng. (July 2024)

Cover Design for *Media Matters in Land-scape Architecture*. (Sept 2024)

NOON Studio, Internship

Oct 2023 – Dec 2023 New York, US

Branding

Led the concept design and fabrication of Gables Baldwin Park's identity. (Oct 2023)

Video Design

Developed seasonal video wall concepts for Zero Irving. (Nov 2023)

Packaging Design & Branding

Designed New Year merchandise and e-blasts for NOON studio, enhancing brand visibility and engagement with target audiences. (Nov 2023–Dec 2023)

Education

Parsons School of Design (BFA)

2020-24

Major: Communication Design (STEM program)

Minor: Photography Honours: Dean's list

Skills Typography Coding
Branding Sketching
Editorial Motion Graphic
Photography Book Production

Language Procifiency

Native in Mandarin, Proficient in English.

Software and Visualization

Adobe Creative Suite

including InDesign, Photoshop, Illustrator, Premiere, After Effect, and Lightroom

Photography

DSLRs, digital cinema cameras and accessories, lighting for portrait photoshooting, and analog photography.

Website Coding Languages

HTML, CSS and Javascript

Figma

Typetool 3